<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dynamo-Browse</title>
    <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dynamo-Browse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/customising/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/customising/</guid>
      <description>Customising Dynamo-Browse #  Some commands can be used to customise Dynamo-Browse, such as modify key bindings. The effect of these commands will only be applied for the duration of the session: they are currently not tracked within the workspace file. So in order to keep customisations across relaunches, these commands can be added to an RC file.
The RC File #  The RC file is a text file containing commands that will be executed by Dynamo-Browse upon launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/editing-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/editing-items/</guid>
      <description>Editing Items #  Dynamo-Browse offers some basic facilities for editing items — such as creating items, deleting items, and modifying their attribute values.
 Marking Items #  Most modifications are applied to items that are marked. A marked item is indicated by a grey background and a bullet indicator (•) on the left side of the table.
To mark or unmark the selected item, press m.
The command unmark can be used to clear all marked items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/filtering-querying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/filtering-querying/</guid>
      <description>Querying And Viewing Results #  Querying #   A query or scan over the table can be performed by entering a Query Expression. Query expressions are a built-in expression language which translates to either a DynamoDB query or scan, depending on the expression. Details about the Query Expression language can be found in the Query Expressions references.
To run a query, press ?, and enter the query expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/getting-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/getting-around/</guid>
      <description>Getting Around #  After selecting a table, Dynamo-Browse will perform a scan and present the results in the default view mode.
 This mode consists of three panes:
 The top pane displays the result-set of the last scan or query. The table name is at the top-left. The middle pane displays the attributes of the currently selected item, along with their type. The bottom pane displays the current query or filter, plus any messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/launching/</guid>
      <description>Launching And Quitting #  To launch Dynamo-Browse, run the following command at the terminal:
dynamo-browse This will use your current AWS configuration and region, which can be changed by setting the relevant AWS_ environment variables.
To connect to a local instance of DynamoDB, such as one running in a Docker container, use the --local flag. This takes as the argument the hostname and endpoint of the local DynamoDB server. The hostname can be omitted, and will default to localhost:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/commands/</guid>
      <description>Commands #  del-attr #  :del-attr &amp;lt;attribute&amp;gt; Alias: da
Deletes attribute from the currently selected item; or if there are any marked items, the marked items.
delete #  :delete Deletes the marked items. Unlike the other commands that modify items, this command will be executed on the table straight away.
echo #  :echo [message ...] Displays message in the status bar. Mainly used for debugging.
export #  :export &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; Writes the currently loaded items as a CSV file to filename.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/key-bindings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/key-bindings/</guid>
      <description>Key Bindings #   Show binding names    Key Binding Name Action     Main View Mode   &amp;uarr;/i table.move-up Move selection up   &amp;darr;/k table.move-down Move selection down   PgUp/&amp;#8679;I table.page-up Page up   PgDn/&amp;#8679;K table.page-down Page down   Home/0 table.goto-top Move selection to first item   End/$ table.goto-bottom Move selection to last item   &amp;larr;/j table.move-left Scroll displayed columns left   &amp;rarr;/l table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/launch-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/launch-flags/</guid>
      <description>Launch Flags #  -debug #  -debug &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; Enable debug logs, which will be written to filename.
-default-limit #  -default-limit &amp;lt;int&amp;gt; Sets the default limit of queries or scans. The default is 1,000 items.
-local #  -local [host]:&amp;lt;port&amp;gt; Connect to a local DynamoDB service listening on host:port. The default host is localhost.
-ro #  -ro Enable read-only mode.
-t #  -t &amp;lt;tableName&amp;gt; Open the table tableName, instead of prompting for a table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/query-expressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/query-expressions/</guid>
      <description>Query Expression #  Query expression is used to execute queries and scans over items in the DynamoDB table. Such expressions can also be used in other areas of Dynamo-Browse, such as populating the value of new columns.
Note that the query expression language is still under early development and may change in the future.  The expression is represented in EBNF form:
string = &#39;&amp;quot;&#39; .* &#39;&amp;quot;&#39;; identifier = [a-zA-Z_][a-zA-Z0-9_]*; literal = string; field = identifier (&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/settings/</guid>
      <description>Settings #  default-limit #   Type: int Default: 1000  The maximum number of rows returned from a query or scan.
ro #   Type: flag  Enable read-only mode. When enabled, all modification operations are disabled, and will fail with a Read-only mode error. The rw setting will disable read-only mode.
rw #   Type: flag  Disable read-only mode. The ro setting will enable read-only mode.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
