<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dynamo-Browse</title>
    <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dynamo-Browse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/customising/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/customising/</guid>
      <description>Customising Dynamo-Browse # Some commands can be used to customise Dynamo-Browse, such as modify key bindings. The effect of these commands will only be applied for the duration of the session: they are currently not tracked within the workspace file. So in order to keep customisations across relaunches, these commands can be added to an RC file.
The RC File # The RC file is a text file containing commands that will be executed by Dynamo-Browse upon launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/editing-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/editing-items/</guid>
      <description>Editing Items # Dynamo-Browse offers some basic facilities for editing items — such as creating items, deleting items, and modifying their attribute values.
Marking Items # Most modifications are applied to items that are marked. A marked item is indicated by a grey background and a bullet indicator (•) on the left side of the table.
To mark or unmark the selected item, press m.
The command unmark can be used to clear all marked items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/filtering-querying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/filtering-querying/</guid>
      <description>Querying And Viewing Results # Querying # A query or scan over the table can be performed by entering a Query Expression. Query expressions are a built-in expression language which translates to either a DynamoDB query or scan, depending on the expression. Details about the Query Expression language can be found in the Query Expressions references.
To run a query, press ?, and enter the query expression.
To clear a query, press ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/getting-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/getting-around/</guid>
      <description>Getting Around # After selecting a table, Dynamo-Browse will perform a scan and present the results in the default view mode.
This mode consists of three panes:
The top pane displays the result-set of the last scan or query. The table name is at the top-left. The middle pane displays the attributes of the currently selected item, along with their type. The bottom pane displays the current query or filter, plus any messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/launching/</guid>
      <description>Launching And Quitting # To launch Dynamo-Browse, run the following command at the terminal:
dynamo-browse This will use your current AWS configuration and region, which can be changed by setting the relevant AWS_ environment variables.
To connect to a local instance of DynamoDB, such as one running in a Docker container, use the --local flag. This takes as the argument the hostname and endpoint of the local DynamoDB server. The hostname can be omitted, and will default to localhost:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/commands/</guid>
      <description>Commands # clone # :clone Copies the currently selected item to a new item, which will appear at the bottom of the table.
Cloning an item will prompt for a new partition key and sort key but will not check for duplicates.
del-attr # :del-attr &amp;lt;attribute&amp;gt; Alias: da
Deletes attribute from the currently selected item; or if there are any marked items, the marked items.
delete # :delete Deletes the marked items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/key-bindings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/key-bindings/</guid>
      <description>Key Bindings # Show binding names Key Binding Name Action Main View Mode &amp;uarr;/i table.move-up Move selection up &amp;darr;/k table.move-down Move selection down PgUp/&amp;#8679;I table.page-up Page up PgDn/&amp;#8679;K table.page-down Page down Home/0 table.goto-top Move selection to first item End/$ table.goto-bottom Move selection to last item &amp;larr;/j table.move-left Scroll displayed columns left &amp;rarr;/l table.move-right Scroll displayed columns right Backspace view.view-back Go back \ view.view-forward Go forward w view.cycle-layout-forward Cycle forward through layout &amp;#8679;W view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/launch-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/launch-flags/</guid>
      <description>Launch Flags # -debug # -debug &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; Enable debug logs, which will be written to filename.
-default-limit # -default-limit &amp;lt;int&amp;gt; Sets the default limit of queries or scans. The default is 1,000 items.
-local # -local [host]:&amp;lt;port&amp;gt; Connect to a local DynamoDB service listening on host:port. The default host is localhost.
-ro # -ro Enable read-only mode.
-t # -t &amp;lt;tableName&amp;gt; Open the table tableName, instead of prompting for a table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/query-expressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/query-expressions/</guid>
      <description>Query Expression # Query expressions are used to select rows of a table. When executed as a query (i.e. by pressing ?), they will be translated into query or table scans that will run over the DynamoDB table in AWS. They work similar to the &amp;ldquo;where&amp;rdquo; clause in PartiQL except that they only require Query and Scan permission on the AWS table and do not require &amp;ldquo;select&amp;rdquo; clauses. Such expressions can also be used in other areas of Dynamo-Browse, such as populating the value of new columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/settings/</guid>
      <description>Settings # default-limit # Type: int Default: 1000 The maximum number of rows returned from a query or scan.
ro # Type: flag Enable read-only mode. When enabled, all modification operations are disabled, and will fail with a Read-only mode error. The rw setting will disable read-only mode.
rw # Type: flag Disable read-only mode. The ro setting will enable read-only mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Script API</title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/script-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/reference/script-api/</guid>
      <description> Script API # </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scripting</title>
      <link>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dynamobrowse.app/docs/scripting/</guid>
      <description>Scripting # Scripts can be used to automate certain tasks with Dynamo-Browse. They can also be used to define new commands or key bindings.
Scripting Basics # Dynamo-Browse scripts are written using the Tamarin scripting language, which looks a lot like Go. All features of the language are available in Dynamo-Browse.
The typical &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; script for Dynamo-Browse is below:
ui.print(&amp;#34;Hello, world&amp;#34;) This uses the ui package, which is the package used to interact with the Dynamo-Browse user interface.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
