<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dynamo-browse on Audax Toolset</title>
    <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dynamo-browse on Audax Toolset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Launching and Quitting</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/launching/</guid>
      <description>To launch Dynamo-Browse, run the following command at the terminal:
dynamo-browse This will use your current AWS configuration and region, which can be changed by setting the relevant AWS_ environment variables.
To connect to a local instance of DynamoDB, such as one running in a Docker container, use the --local flag. This takes as the argument the hostname and endpoint of the local DynamoDB server. The hostname can be omitted, and will default to localhost:</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;To launch Dynamo-Browse, run the following command at the terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;dynamo-browse
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will use your current AWS configuration and region, which can be changed by setting
the relevant &lt;code&gt;AWS_&lt;/code&gt; environment variables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To connect to a local instance of DynamoDB, such as one
running in a Docker container, use the &lt;code&gt;--local&lt;/code&gt; flag.  This takes as the argument the hostname
and endpoint of the local DynamoDB server.  The hostname can be omitted, and will default to &lt;code&gt;localhost&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;dynamo-browse --local :8080
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;selecting-a-table&#34;&gt;Selecting a Table&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon launch, Dynamo-Browse will present a list of all the tables within the region:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://audax.tools/images/dynamo-browse/table-selection.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Table selection&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Select the table to view by pressing &lt;kbd&gt;Enter&lt;/kbd&gt;.  Use the following keys to navigate
the items within the list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;↑&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;i&lt;/kbd&gt;: Move selection up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;↓&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;k&lt;/kbd&gt;: Move selection down&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once the table is selected, the table will be scanned and Dynamo-Browse will be presented in
&lt;a href=&#34;#view-mode&#34;&gt;View Mode&lt;/a&gt;.  Another table can be selected from within view mode using the &lt;code&gt;:table&lt;/code&gt; command.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dynamo-Browse can also be launched directly in view mode by specifying a table using the &lt;code&gt;-t&lt;/code&gt; flag:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;dynamo-browse -t user-accounts
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;selecting-a-workspace&#34;&gt;Selecting a Workspace&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dynamo-Browse tracks session state, such as the back-stack, in a workspace file.  By default the workspace
file will be a new file created within the temporary directory, but a specific workspace filename can be
specified by using the &lt;code&gt;-w&lt;/code&gt; flag:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;dynamo-browse -w my-workspace.ws
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the workspace filename references an existing file, Dynamo-Browse will restore the workspace and use it for the duration of
the session.  If the workspace filename references a non-existing file, Dynamo-Browse will initialise a new workspace
using the specified filename.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only one running instance of Dynamo-Browse can use a single workspace file at any one time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quitting&#34;&gt;Quitting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To quit dynamodb-browse, enter the command &lt;code&gt;q&lt;/code&gt; by pressing &lt;kbd&gt;:&lt;/kbd&gt;, then typing &lt;kbd&gt;q&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;Enter&lt;/kbd&gt;.
The keystroke &lt;kbd&gt;Ctrl+C&lt;/kbd&gt; can also be used to quit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Around</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/getting-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/getting-around/</guid>
      <description>After selecting a table, Dynamo-Browse will perform a scan and present the results in the default view mode.
This mode consists of three panes:
 The top pane displays the result-set of the last scan or query. The table name is at the top-left. The middle pane displays the attributes of the currently selected item, along with their type. The bottom pane displays the current query or filter, plus any messages.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;After selecting a table, Dynamo-Browse will perform a scan and present the results in the default view mode.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://audax.tools/images/dynamo-browse/main-item-view.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Main item view&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This mode consists of three panes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top pane displays the result-set of the last scan or query.  The table name is at the top-left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The middle pane displays the attributes of the currently selected item, along with their type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The bottom pane displays the current query or filter, plus any messages.  Prompts for input will
also appear at the bottom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The result-set is sorted in ascending order based on the value and type of the partition and sort key.
Up to 1,000 rows will be displayed for the current result-set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since DynamoDB does not require all items to have the same attribute (unless they are pre-defined), any
attribute not set for a column is indicated with a grey tilde character &lt;code&gt;~&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use the following keys to change the currently selected row, which is highlighted in purple:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;↑&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;i&lt;/kbd&gt;: Move selection up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;↓&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;k&lt;/kbd&gt;: Move selection down&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;PgUp&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;⇧ I&lt;/kbd&gt;: Page up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;PgDn&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;⇧ K&lt;/kbd&gt;: Page down&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;Home&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;0&lt;/kbd&gt;: First row&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;End&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;$&lt;/kbd&gt;: Last row&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The columns of the table
consist of the top-level attributes of the result-set.  The partition key, sort key, plus any explicitly defined
attributes will always be displayed from the left margin onwards.  The other attributes are determined
from the results of the last scan or query, and may change depending on the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The display columns of the table can be scrolled across by using the following keys:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;←&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;j&lt;/kbd&gt;: Scroll to the left&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;→&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;l&lt;/kbd&gt;: Scroll to the right&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The attributes of the currently selected item will appear in the middle pane.  Both the type and the value of each
attribute will be displayed.  Any nested attributes will be indented, and will below their parent item.  A value
displayed in grey does not represent the actual value of the item, but indicates some meta-information about the item,
such as the length.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-back-stack&#34;&gt;The Back-stack&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changes to the view of Dynamo-Browse will be maintained in back-stack, similar to how a
web-browse keeps track of the webpages you&amp;rsquo;ve visited.  This stack will record the
currently viewed table, filter, or query, allowing you to &amp;ldquo;go back&amp;rdquo; to a previous view
by pressing &lt;kbd&gt;Backspace&lt;/kbd&gt;.  Pressing &lt;kbd&gt;\&lt;/kbd&gt; will allow you to go forward through the stack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The back-stack is preserved in the workspace file, and can be restored by launching Dynamo-Browse with the &lt;code&gt;-w&lt;/code&gt;
switch.  Launching Dynamo-Browse with a workspace that has a non-empty stack will restore the last viewed
table, filter, or query from the session that was previously using the workspace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;framed&#34;&gt;
  Note that the back-stack does not preserve the actual items in the workspace.  Going backwards or forwards
  through the back-stack will execute any queries or filters against the actual table itself.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;adjusting-the-layout&#34;&gt;Adjusting The Layout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The horizontal size of the item table and currently selected item pane can be changed to one of the
following layout configurations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item view taking up 14 rows on the bottom with the table pane taking up the rest of the vertical space (the default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item view and table view taking up half of the available space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table view taking up 7 rows on the top with the item view taking up the rest of the vertical space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table view hidden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item view hidden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pressing &lt;kbd&gt;w&lt;/kbd&gt; will cycle forward though these layouts.  For example, while in the
default layout, pressing &lt;kbd&gt;w&lt;/kbd&gt; will switch to the second layout, where both the table view take up half the
screen.  Pressing &lt;kbd&gt;⇧ W&lt;/kbd&gt; will cycle through the layouts in the reverse order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;entering-commands&#34;&gt;Entering Commands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commands can be entered by pressing &lt;kbd&gt;:&lt;/kbd&gt; and entering the command, with any arguments, at the prompt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The list of available commands can be found within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/reference/#commands&#34;&gt;reference section&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtering and Querying</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/filtering-querying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/filtering-querying/</guid>
      <description>Filtering The displayed items of the current result-set can be filtered down to those that contain a specific substring.
To set the filter, press /, and enter the substring you wish to filter on.
To clear the filter, press /, and press Enter without entering any value.
When a filter is set, any item that does not have a top-level attribute containing the substring will be hidden.
Filtering will only consist the items that are in the current result-set.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;filtering&#34;&gt;Filtering&lt;/h2&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://audax.tools/images/dynamo-browse/filter-items.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Items with filter applied&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The displayed items of the current result-set can be filtered down to those that contain a specific substring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To set the filter, press &lt;kbd&gt;/&lt;/kbd&gt;, and enter the substring you wish to filter on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clear the filter, press &lt;kbd&gt;/&lt;/kbd&gt;, and press &lt;kbd&gt;Enter&lt;/kbd&gt; without entering any value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a filter is set, any item that does not have a top-level attribute containing the substring will be hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Filtering will only consist the items that are in the current result-set.  It will not result in a call to the actual
table itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that filtering is case sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;querying&#34;&gt;Querying&lt;/h2&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://audax.tools/images/dynamo-browse/query-items.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Items with query applied&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;A query or scan over the table can be made by entering a query expression.
Query expressions are a built-in expression language which translates to either a DynamoDB query
or scan, depending on the expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To run a query, press &lt;kbd&gt;?&lt;/kbd&gt;, and enter the query expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clear a query, press &lt;kbd&gt;?&lt;/kbd&gt;, and press &lt;kbd&gt;Enter&lt;/kbd&gt; without entering any value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;framed&#34;&gt;
  Note that the query expression language is still under early development and may change in the future.
  At the moment, all query expressions result in a table scan.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The types of query expressions that are supported are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;attr = &amp;quot;value&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;: matches items where attribute &lt;em&gt;attr&lt;/em&gt; matches the string &lt;em&gt;value&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;attr ^= &amp;quot;value&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;: matches items where attribute &lt;em&gt;attr&lt;/em&gt; has the prefix &lt;em&gt;value&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing Items</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/editing-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/editing-items/</guid>
      <description>Dynamo-Browse offers some basic facilities for editing items — such as creating items, deleting items, and modifying their attribute values.
Marking Items Most modifications are applied to items that are marked. A marked item is indicated by a grey background and a bullet indicator (•) on the left side of the table.
To mark or unmark the selected item, press m.
The command unmark can be used to clear all marked items.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Dynamo-Browse offers some basic facilities for editing items — such as creating items, deleting items,
and modifying their attribute values.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://audax.tools/images/dynamo-browse/modified-items.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Item indicators&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;marking-items&#34;&gt;Marking Items&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most modifications are applied to items that are marked.  A marked item is indicated by a grey
background and a bullet indicator (&lt;code&gt;•&lt;/code&gt;) on the left side of the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To mark or unmark the selected item, press &lt;kbd&gt;m&lt;/kbd&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The command &lt;code&gt;unmark&lt;/code&gt; can be used to clear all marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;modifying-attributes&#34;&gt;Modifying Attributes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Item attributes can be added or modified by using the command &lt;code&gt;set-attr&lt;/code&gt; or the alias &lt;code&gt;sa&lt;/code&gt;.
This command can be used to modify the value and type of an attribute of the currently selected items, or
from any marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The format of the command is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:set-attr [&amp;lt;type&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;attributeName&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where type is one of the following (case insensitive):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-S&lt;/code&gt;: string&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-N&lt;/code&gt;: number&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-BOOL&lt;/code&gt;: boolean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-NULL&lt;/code&gt;: null&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the type is not specified, and the attribute exists, then the attribute type will not change.
The type must be specified if this is a new attribute or multiple items have been marked.
After executing the command, Dynamo-Browse will prompt for the value of the new attribute if one is
required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modified attributes will only be tracked in memory: they will not be written
to the actual table until it is &amp;ldquo;putted&amp;rdquo; (see &lt;a href=&#34;#committing-changes&#34;&gt;Committing Changes&lt;/a&gt;).
An item that has been modified will be displayed in red and a modified indicator (&lt;code&gt;M&lt;/code&gt;) will appear
on the left-most column.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;deleting-attributes&#34;&gt;Deleting Attributes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An attribute can be deleted by using the command &lt;code&gt;del-attr&lt;/code&gt; or the alias &lt;code&gt;da&lt;/code&gt;.  The format of the command
is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:del-attr &amp;lt;attributeName&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;When executed, the attribute with the name &lt;em&gt;attributeName&lt;/em&gt; will be deleted from the selected item, or
from any marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deleted attributes will only be tracked in memory: they will not be removed from
the actual table until it is &amp;ldquo;putted&amp;rdquo; (see &lt;a href=&#34;#committing-changes&#34;&gt;Committing Changes&lt;/a&gt;).
An item that has been modified will be displayed in red and a modified indicator (&lt;code&gt;M&lt;/code&gt;) will appear
on the left-most column.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;adding-items&#34;&gt;Adding Items&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new item can be created by typing in the command &lt;code&gt;new-item&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When entered, Dynamo-Browse will prompt for the partition and sort key.  Once these are entered,
the item will appear in the top pane in green with an asterisk indicator (&lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt;) on the left left-most column.
Any additional attributes can be set by using &lt;code&gt;set-attr&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new item will only appear in memory: it will not be written
to the actual table until it is &amp;ldquo;putted&amp;rdquo; (see &lt;a href=&#34;#committing-changes&#34;&gt;Committing Changes&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;deleting-items&#34;&gt;Deleting Items&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Items can be deleted by marking them and then typing in the command &lt;code&gt;delete&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike most of the other modified commands, running &lt;code&gt;delete&lt;/code&gt; WILL make changes to the table
immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;committing-changes&#34;&gt;Committing Changes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New or modified items (but not deleted items) will be kept in memory until they are committed
or &amp;ldquo;putted&amp;rdquo; to the table.  To put the changes, use the &lt;code&gt;put&lt;/code&gt; command or &lt;code&gt;w&lt;/code&gt; alias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;backing-out-of-changes&#34;&gt;Backing Out of Changes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any modified items can be reverted back to what they are in the actual table by rerunning the
current query.  This can be done by pressing &lt;kbd&gt;⇧ R&lt;/kbd&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customising Dynamo-Browse</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/customising/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/customising/</guid>
      <description>Some commands can be used to customise Dynamo-Browse, such as modify key bindings. The effect of these commands will only be applied for the duration of the session: they are currently not tracked within the workspace file. So in order to keep customisations across relaunches, these commands can be added to an RC file.
The RC File The RC file is a text file containing commands that will be executed by Dynamo-Browse upon launch.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Some commands can be used to customise Dynamo-Browse, such as modify key bindings.
The effect of these commands will only be applied for the duration of the session: they are currently not
tracked within the workspace file.  So in order to keep customisations across relaunches, these commands
can be added to an RC file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-rc-file&#34;&gt;The RC File&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RC file is a text file containing commands that will be executed by Dynamo-Browse upon launch.
By default, the RC file is located at the following path:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$HOME/.config/audax/dynamo-browse/init.rc
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;This file is primarily intended for commands that customise Dynamo-Browse in a particular way, but any
command can be entered here.  If this file is found, Dynamo-Browse will invoke each command before loading
or prompting the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;rebinding-keys&#34;&gt;Rebinding Keys&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The default key bindings of Dynamo-Browse can be changed using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/reference/#rebind&#34;&gt;rebind&lt;/a&gt; command.  This takes
a binding name corresponding to the particular action to invoke, and the key
to which it should be mapped to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Putting these commands in the RC file will effectively change the default bindings of Dynamo-Browse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Rebind T to prompt for a table
rebind &amp;quot;view.prompt-for-table&amp;quot; &amp;quot;T&amp;quot;

# Rebind escape to prompt for a command
rebind &amp;quot;view.prompt-for-command&amp;quot; &amp;quot;esc&amp;quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the moment each binding name can only be mapped to a single key.  It&amp;rsquo;s also currently not possible
to setup bindings for commands.  These may be supported in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list of available binding names can be found the the &lt;a href=&#34;https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/reference/#key-bindings&#34;&gt;reference&lt;/a&gt;
(check the &amp;ldquo;Show binding names&amp;rdquo; checkbox).  Note that some bindings may not have default key bindings.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audax.tools/docs/dynamo-browse/reference/</guid>
      <description>Key Bindings  Show binding names    Key Binding Name Action     &amp;uarr;/i table.move-up Move selection up   &amp;darr;/k table.move-down Move selection down   PgUp/&amp;#8679;I table.page-up Page up   PgDn/&amp;#8679;K table.page-down Page down   Home/0 table.goto-top Move selection to first item   End/$ table.goto-bottom Move selection to last item   &amp;larr;/j table.move-left Shift displayed columns left   &amp;rarr;/l table.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;key-bindings&#34;&gt;Key Bindings&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div data-controller=&#34;keybindings&#34;&gt;
&lt;label&gt;
	&lt;input type=&#34;checkbox&#34; id=&#34;show-kb-binding-names&#34; 
    data-keybindings-target=&#34;showBindingNames&#34; data-action=&#34;keybindings#bindingNamesChanged&#34;&gt; Show binding names
&lt;/label&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;key-bindings&#34; data-keybindings-target=&#34;keyBindingTable&#34;&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;th class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34; style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Key&lt;/th&gt;
  &lt;th class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34; style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Binding Name&lt;/th&gt;
  &lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Action&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;uarr;&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;i&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.move-up&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Move selection up&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;darr;&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;k&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.move-down&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Move selection down&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;PgUp&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;#8679;I&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.page-up&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Page up&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;PgDn&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;#8679;K&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.page-down&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Page down&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;Home&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;0&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.goto-top&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Move selection to first item&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;End&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;$&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.goto-bottom&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Move selection to last item&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;larr;&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;j&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.move-left&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Shift displayed columns left&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;rarr;&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;l&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;table.move-right&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Shift displayed columns right&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;Backspace&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.view-back&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Go back&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;\&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.view-forward&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Go forward&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;w&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.cycle-layout-forward&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Cycle forward through layout&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;&amp;#8679;W&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.cycle-layout-backwards&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Cycle backwards through layout&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;m&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.mark&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Mark/unmark currently selected item&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;c&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.copy-item-to-clipboard&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Copy displayed item to pasteboard&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;/&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.prompt-for-filter&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Filter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;?&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.prompt-for-query&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Run scan/query&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.prompt-for-table&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Select table&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;R&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.rescan&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Rerun last scan/query&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;:&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.prompt-for-command&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Enter command&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-key-binding&#34;&gt;&lt;kbd&gt;^C&lt;/kbd&gt;/&lt;kbd&gt;Esc&lt;/kbd&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class=&#34;kb-binding-name&#34;&gt;view.quit&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td&gt;Quit&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;commands&#34;&gt;Commands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;del-attr&#34;&gt;del-attr&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:del-attr &amp;lt;attribute&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alias: &lt;code&gt;da&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deletes &lt;em&gt;attribute&lt;/em&gt; from the currently selected item; or if there are any marked items, the marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;delete&#34;&gt;delete&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:delete
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deletes the marked items.  Unlike the other commands that modify items, this command will be executed on
the table straight away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;echo&#34;&gt;echo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:echo [message ...]
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Displays &lt;em&gt;message&lt;/em&gt; in the status bar.  Mainly used for debugging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;export&#34;&gt;export&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:export &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Writes the currently loaded items as a CSV file to &lt;em&gt;filename&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;new-item&#34;&gt;new-item&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:new-item
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creates a new item.  When executed, the value for the partition key and sort key will be prompted.
The new item will not be written to the table until it is committed with the &lt;code&gt;put&lt;/code&gt; command.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;put&#34;&gt;put&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:put
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alias: &lt;code&gt;w&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commits all new and modified items to the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;quit&#34;&gt;quit&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:quit
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alias: &lt;code&gt;q&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quits Dynamo-Browse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;rebind&#34;&gt;rebind&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:rebind &amp;lt;bindingName&amp;gt; &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rebinds the action with &lt;em&gt;bindingName&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;em&gt;key&lt;/em&gt;.  This will replace any existing binding for that action.
See &lt;a href=&#34;#key-bindings&#34;&gt;Key Bindings&lt;/a&gt; with &amp;ldquo;Show binding names&amp;rdquo; checked to see available binding names.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;set-attr&#34;&gt;set-attr&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:set-attr [type] &amp;lt;attributeName&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alias: &lt;code&gt;sa&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modifies the value of &lt;em&gt;attribute&lt;/em&gt; of the currently selected item; or if there are any marked items, the marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The value of &lt;em&gt;type&lt;/em&gt; can be use to specify the type of the attribute.  It can be one of the following (case insensitive):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-S&lt;/code&gt;: string value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-N&lt;/code&gt;: number value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-BOOL&lt;/code&gt;: boolean value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-NULL&lt;/code&gt;: null value&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If unset, the attribute type will not be changed.  &lt;em&gt;type&lt;/em&gt; must be set if multiple items have been marked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:table
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Select the table to display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;unmark&#34;&gt;unmark&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;:unmark
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unmark all marked items.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
